scripted.com 2010-02-25

# Scripped - Privacy Policy

## At Scripped we know your information is very important and we take your privacy seriously.

_Effective as of December 27, 2007_

Here at [Scripped.com](http://scripped.com/), (“Scripped”, “we” and “us”), we understand and respect your concerns about the use of your personal information. We believe that you should know what information about you we collect, as well as how that information is used, maintained, and, in some cases, shared. The following sets forth our privacy practices and policies (“Privacy Policy”):

We will collect information about you when you register for our website or other features and services we provide, when you transmit information via our website or by email, when you register for our promotions and when you otherwise use our website. By doing any of the foregoing, you assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not engage in any of these activities.

As described in greater detail below, we will store and use information about you, including information about where and when you browse on our website, to continually improve the quality of our business and our website. 

We will not sell or disclose to unaffiliated third parties without your consent information that we collect about you, except that we may share non-personal, aggregate, or summary information regarding our users with unaffiliated third parties. Such information does not identify you individually, but is often used to provide general demographics or statistics.

### INFORMATION COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AND OUR USE OF SUCH INFORMATION

The following describes the types of personal and other information we may collect about you, and how we use and maintain that information:

#### Contact Information

We collect your contact information when you register for or subscribe to our website or other services and features we provide, when you transmit information via our website or by email, and when you otherwise use our website. Specifically, we may collect and store in a database your name, mailing address, phone number, email address and any other information you provide to us when registering with our website.

We use this information to contact you with regard to your account and/or subscription to our website. We also use this information to respond to any inquiries you may submit to us. In addition, we may use this information to send you periodic publications or news associated with Scripped or promotional materials about Scripped, unless you inform us that you opt out from receiving such communications via email. We also use your contact information to help operate our website. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to your use of our website, such as service announcements, administrative messages and communications regarding your account, subscription, or materials you have posted, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

#### Website Information

Our website collects aggregate information site-wide, including anonymous site statistics. Our website also employs browser cookies to store users' preferences and record session information. “Cookies” are bits of information that are stored by your browser on your hard drive. This technology allows you to save your preferences, if applicable, and remembers you when you take action on our website. You can turn off the “cookie” function through most standard browsers.

In addition, when you visit our website our system automatically collects domain names, your IP address and the type of browser that you use. When you browse our website, our systems log the Scripped web pages that you visit. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the website, improve the design of our website, track user movement, protect copyrighted materials, and otherwise enhance the services we provide. 

Scripped lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. 

#### Information from Promotions

We will collect information you give us if you participate in a Scripped promotion, such as a contest. You may be asked to provide your name and email address, and possibly other information such as your mailing address and telephone number.

We will store this information in our database and will use it to communicate with you about the promotion. We may also use this information to send you periodic publications or news associated with Scripped in the future or promotional materials about Scripped, unless you inform us that you opt out from receiving such communications.

If a promotion is done jointly with another entity, the information we collect may be shared with such third parties who have their own, separate privacy policies. In such a case, you should visit their website(s) to read each applicable privacy policy.

#### Payment Information

If you have a paid subscription to our website, your payment information, such as a credit card number and expiration date, may be stored. We may use the information you provide us to bill you for the products and services you have requested, or to notify you of additional products and services available to you. By subscribing, you agree that we may share this information with our service providers, which may include banks and credit card companies we use to process your transaction.

We take reasonable precautions to protect your payment information from loss, misuse or alteration. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to protect sensitive information such as your credit card number and a series of firewalls to protect our internal systems. However, while processing credit card purchases through such systems is reported to be as safe or safer than many other traditional means, there is always a risk that such information could be obtained by an unauthorized third party.

#### Other Information

We may retain any data you provide to us in an email or other inquiry, for the purpose of tracking the types of questions that we receive. Additionally, to effectuate the intent of our website to reduce costs to screenwriters and introduce collaboration into the writing process, we may store any written, audio, video or material you submit to or through our website, including but not limited to, material submitted or posted to or through our community forums, messaging and chat features, web logs, user profiles, writer groups, and script-authoring application.

Notwithstanding anything contained herein, we will disclose non-personally identifiable information to other companies that we contract with to create, support, manage, maintain or improve our website and the features on our website.

### WHEN YOUR INFORMATION WILL BE SHARED OR DISCLOSED

We may provide your name, mailing address, phone number and email address to affiliates of Scripped and other companies for use in the marketing and promotion of Scripped only with your consent. Otherwise we will only provide non-personally identifiable aggregate data.

We will comply with any subpoenas, court orders or other legal processes for any of the information about you in our possession, and we may use such information to establish or exercise our legal rights, or to defend against legal claims.

We reserve the right to disclose information about you, including data on which pages you have visited, to third parties if we feel it is necessary to protect our systems, business, users or others.

We may provide aggregate information, such as the number of users who have visited our website, to other parties.

Information about you in our possession may also be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, sale of company assets, or transition of service to another provider, as well as in the unlikely event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which your personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company. Scripped does not guarantee that any entity receiving such information in connection with one of these transactions will comply with all terms of this Privacy Policy.

In addition, when you use certain features on our website, such as posting or visiting our community forums, messaging or chatting with other users, creating a profile page, or writing a web log, your “user name” and other information you disclose will be viewable by other users of our website.

#### Security

Whenever Scripped handles information that you enter on our website, regardless of where this occurs, we take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, Scripped cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

Our site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, modification or alteration of the information under our control. Such measures include, but are not limited to, text-to-image conversion, pagination, oversight and backups of all Scripped.com databases, IP address tracking, and implementation of the latest PHP, MySQL and Linux libraries and functions, and records of user access to Materials.

### THIRD PARTY INFORMATION

You agree that you have provided notice to, and obtained consent from, any third party individuals whose personal information you supply to us with regard to: (a) the purposes for which such third party's personal information has been collected; (b) the intended recipients or categories of recipients of the third party's personal information; (c) which of the third party's information is obligatory and which information, if any, is voluntary; and (d) how the third party can access and, if necessary, rectify the information held about them.

### CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

If you are under the age of 13, please do not use or access this Site in any way. We will not knowingly collect or use any personal information from such children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have collected any personal information from children under 13, we will promptly delete such information from our databases.

### OTHER WEBSITES

For your convenience, this website may contain links to other websites, or you may be otherwise referred to other websites, including websites administered by Scripped or administered by other companies on behalf of Scripped, as well as to websites unrelated to Scripped. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these linked websites. Each website should be checked for its own privacy policy.

### CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

Scripped may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. In the event that Scripped merges with, or is acquired by another company, a change to this Privacy Policy may result. Whenever a change to this Privacy Policy is significant, we will place a prominent notice on this website.

### GOVERNING LAW

By choosing to visit this website or otherwise provide information to Scripped, you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy will be governed by the laws of the State of California. You also agree to arbitrate such disputes and to abide by any limitation on damages contained in our Terms of Use (available at [http://www.scripped.com/term](http://scripped.com/term)) or other agreement we have with you.

### UPDATE INFORMATION / SUGGESTIONS

If you would like to update or correct any information that you have provided to Scripped through your use of this website or otherwise, or you have suggestions for improving this Privacy Policy, please send an email to [legal@scripped.com](mailto:%20legal@scripped.com).
